{
    "subject": "resource/Tapulous",
    "predicate": "ontology/foundationPlace",
    "object": "resource/Palo_Alto,_California",
    "human_readable": "Tapulous was founded in Palo Alto, California.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8069338798522949,
            "question": "Where was Tapulous founded?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7632744312286377,
            "question": "In what state was Tapulous founded?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.743937075138092,
            "question": "Who were the founders of Tapulous?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6975330710411072,
            "question": "When was Tapulous founded?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5460110306739807,
            "question": "What is the name of the company that Tapulous founded?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.444385290145874,
            "question": "Was Tapulous acquired by another company?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23289541900157928,
            "question": "What products or services did Tapulous offer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21860970556735992,
            "question": "What type of company is Tapulous?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1208823174238205,
            "question": "Are there any popular games associated with Tapulous?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.08085644245147705,
            "question": "What impact did Tapulous have on the mobile gaming industry?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Tapulous was founded in Palo Alto, California.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4813_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any popular games associated with Tapulous?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4813_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of company is Tapulous?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4813_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What products or services did Tapulous offer?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4813_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4813_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4813_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4813_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4813_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4813_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4813_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4813_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4813_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4813_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4813_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format answer:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that the documents all confirm that Tapulous was indeed founded in Palo Alto, California. This information appears in multiple files (32.txt, 33.txt, and 88.txt), which provides strong evidence to support this triple statement."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis answer is derived from the information provided in the documents which state that Tapulous is headquartered in Palo Alto, California. The documents also mention that it was a wholly owned subsidiary of Disney Mobile as part of the Disney Interactive Media Group, further confirming its location and status as described in the triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}